import quest1 from "../assets/quest1.avif";
import quest2 from "../assets/quest2.avif";
import quest3 from "../assets/quest3.avif";
import quest4 from "../assets/quest4.avif";
import quest5 from "../assets/pink.avif";
import quest6 from "../assets/quest6.avif";
import quest7 from "../assets/quest7.avif";
import quest8 from "../assets/quest8.avif";
import quest9 from "../assets/quest9.avif";
import quest10 from "../assets/gran.avif";

const questions = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "Which pony lives in the Ponyville library?",
    options: ["Rarity", "Twilight Sparkle", "Applejack", "Pinkie Pie"],
    solution: "Twilight Sparkle",
    img: quest1,
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "Which element of harmony does Rainbow Dash represent?",
    options: ["Kindness", "Loyalty", "Generosity", "Honesty"],
    solution: "Loyalty",
    img: quest2,
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "What is the name of the little dragon who accompanies Twilight?",
    options: ["Spike", "Smolder", "Scorch", "Flame"],
    solution: "Spike",
    img: quest3,
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "Where does Rarity work?",
    options: [
      "Sweet Apple Acres",
      "Carousel Boutique",
      "Canterlot Castle",
      "The Library",
    ],
    solution: "Carousel Boutique",
    img: quest4,
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "What pet does Pinkie Pie have?",
    options: [
      "A bunny named Angel",
      "A goose named Marshmallow",
      "An alligator named Gummy",
      "An owl named Owlowiscious",
    ],
    solution: "An alligator named Gummy",
    img: quest5,
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "When does a pony get her cutie mark?",
    options: [
      "When she is born",
      "When she discovers what makes her special",
      "When she reaches a certain age",
      "When she learns a magic spell",
    ],
    solution: "When she discovers what makes her special",
    img: quest6,
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "Who was the first villain in Season 1?",
    options: ["Sunset Shimmer", "Nightmare Moon", "Discord", "King Sombra"],
    solution: "Nightmare Moon",
    img: quest7,
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question:
      "Which creature invades Ponyville in the episode “Boast Busters”?",
    options: ["Hydra", "Ursa Major", "Ursa Minor", "Manticore"],
    solution: "Ursa Minor",
    img: quest8,
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question:
      "What is the name of the snake the ponies use as a bridge in 'Friendship Is Magic Part 2'?",
    options: ["Fred", "Steven", "George", "Bill"],
    solution: "Steven",
    img: quest9,
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question:
      "What annual event is held in Canterlot that appears on the show?",
    options: [
      "Spring Festival",
      "The Grand Galloping Gala",
      "Friendship Day",
      "Magic Contest",
    ],
    solution: "The Grand Galloping Gala",
    img: quest10,
  },
];

export default questions;
